Damnit! A battle of strength is the only way after all!
Now it's time for you to be crushed under my foot!!
Crush me if you can!
Running away? Futile!
Take this, Hunter Missiles!
What, just gonna run away?
Then I'll have to go on the offensive!
Pervert!!
My clothes!!
How's that? Keep running, and it'll only get worse!
That's it, you damn coward!!
No more running, come at me head-on!
You better not run, hahaha!
I'll blow your clothes off as well!!
Hunter Mirror!
Confess already!
You were controlling all the oyaji and making them harass women!
Shut up!! Women were the ones who harassed me first!
I just wanted to get back at them for bullying me!
Oh hey, you're just a little runt!
You're just like them! Calling me shortstop,
baldy, Gollum, disgusting gnome, it's not fair!!
That's it!! I'll make a bigger robot next time, and I'll... I'll blow you all away...
Ahh, I'm sorry... I shouldn't have called you a runt...
So don't blow us all away, okay?
No way!
Mister, we'll apologize for all the rude women in their place:
We're sorry!
Thank you... everyone...
Nice people do exist...
I promise I won't be evil anymore...
- Goodbye!
- Bye bye!