Huh...? What am I doing here...?
Don't try and weasel yourself out of this now!
An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
S&M for S&M.
You picked the wrong woman.
Just who do you think I am!?
I'm the Beautiful Rider!
Don't disrespect the way of bondage!
Mistress, please st—
P-please don't stop!
Please punish me!
I think that's plenty...
No way! Thank you for helping me.
I'm okay now, so you can leave us here.
You shitty old man!!
I'm in Heaven! Please don't stop!
I'm begging you! ♥
Understand now? No need to interrupt us.
But you're hitting him kind of hard...
He's begging me for it, what's the problem?
Nevermind, uh, go ahead...
It feels so good!! ♥
I guess that's that.
More... More...!
I can't get enough...
Well then, keep it consensual!
Bye bye, Oyaji Hunter!