Marin-chan~ Funny as always!
Hey lady, have some taiyaki!
It's super good!
Come on, open up!
- N-no thanks...
I said I'm fine!
No need to be shy~!
Here comes the plane~! Doesn't it look tasty?
Here, here! Delicious, right? Plenty more, don't be shy!
Was that gag too much for you?
Use this, we can spit roast the rest!
HELP!
Hunter... Yo-yo!
Look what you did to my tasty balls!
Oyaji Hunter has landed!
Can't you tell how annoying you are with your takoyaki gag?
It's curtains for you, pushy oyaji!
Step off, heckler!
Well then, have a taste of your own gag!
The takoyaki harasser oyaji has become a takoyaki cannibal!
Maybe we should cook you up and open a takoyaki shop here?
We'll just have to settle this with mahjong then!!